Guide to the Daily Worker and Daily World Cartoon Collection GRAPHICS.024.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Biographical Cartoons, 1936-1994
  - Mannerheim, Gustav, undated (Box 1, Folder 242)
  - Manuel, Major, undated (Box 1, Folder 243)
  - Mao Tse-Tung, undated (Box 1, Folder 244)
  - Markoff, Abraham, undated (Box 1, Folder 245)
  - Marshall, George C. (George Catlett), undated (Box 1, Folder 246)
  - Martin, Joseph W. (Joseph William), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 247)
  - Martin, Warren Homer, 1938, undated (Box 1, Folder 248)
  - Marzani, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Mason, Thad, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - McAdoo, William Gibbs, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - McCarren, Pat, 1939, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - McCormick, Robert A., undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - McDonald, David J. (David John), undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - McKeller, Kenneth Douglas, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - McNamara, Robert S., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - McNutt, Paul V. (Paul Vories), undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meany, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Medina, Harold R. (Harold Raymond), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Miaja Menant, Jose, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Middleton, C. W., undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mihailovic, Draza, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mincey, Pamela, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell, John N. (John Newton), undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Molotov, Vyacheslav Mikhaylovich, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Moore, Edward Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Morgan, Arthur Ernest, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Morgan, Frederick Edgeworth, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Morris, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mosley, Oswald, 1939, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mundt, Karl E. (Karl Earl), undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Murphy, Michael Joseph, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Murray, Philip, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Murray, William H. (William Henry), undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Nasser, Gamal Abdel, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Nelson, Steve, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Nenni, Pietro, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Neruda, Pablo, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Nimitz, Charles W. (Chester William), undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Nixon, Richard I, 1968-1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Nixon, Richard II, 1968-1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Nixon, Richard III, 1968-1972, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Oatis, William Nathan, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - O'Donnell, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - O'Dwyer, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Olds, Irving, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - O'Neal, Edward Asbury, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Patterson, Joseph Medill, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Patterson, William L. (William Lorenzo), undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Paul VI, Pope, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Pavlichenko, Liudmila Mikhailovna, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Peltier, Leonard, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Perkins, Frances, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Perlo, Victor, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Pepper, Claude, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Peron, Juan Domingo, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Pieck, Wilhelm, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Pinochet Ugarte, Augusto, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Pitcaim, Frank, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Pollitt, Henry, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Potash, Irving, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Quezon, Manuel Luis, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Quin, Mike, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Quinn, May, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Queipo de Llano, Conzalo, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Asa Philip), undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Rankin, John E. (John Elliott), undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Rayburn, Sam, 1949, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Reagan, Ronald, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Reed, Clyde M., 1943 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Refrigerier, Auton, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Reiner, Fritz, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Renn, Ludwig, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Revels, Hiram R., undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Reuther, Walter, 1950, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Reynolds, Robert Rice, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Rhee, Syngman, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Richards, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Richardson, Elliot L., undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Ridgeway, Matthew B., undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Riesel, Victor, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Rivers, Ed, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Robinson, Jackie, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Robeson, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Roca Calderio, Blas, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Rochester, Anna, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Rockefeller, John D. (John Davison), Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1959, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Rolland, Romain, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Roosevelt, Elliot, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Roper, Daniel C. (Daniel Calhoun), undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Rogue, Ana, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Rose, Alex, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Russell, Richard B. (Richard Brevard), Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Ryan, Joseph P. (Joseph Patrick), undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Schuster, Joseph, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Seaver, Ed, undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Sentner, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Seur, Alexander, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Shields, Art, 1971, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Shivers, Allan, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Sinclair, Upton, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Siqueiros, David Alfaro, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Small, John D., undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Smith, Ferdinand, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Smith, Gerald L. K. (Gerald Lyman Kenneth), undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Smith, Howard Worth, undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Snell, Bertrand Hollis, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Snyder, John W. (John Wesley), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr Isaevich, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Soong, T. V. (Tzu-Wen), undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Spangler, Charles E., 1943 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Spangler, Harrison E. (Harrison Earl), undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Sparkman, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Spring, Harold, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Stassen, Harold Edward, undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Stellato, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 110a)
  - Steavig, Charles A., undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Stettinius, Edward R., undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Stimson, Henry L. (Henry Lewis), 1942 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Stirling, Yates, undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Stokowski, Leopold, undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Stone, Lucy, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Strachey, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Stratemeyer, George E., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Stratton, William G., undated (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Swank, Harold O., undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Stalin, Joseph, undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Taft, Robert A. (Robert Alphonso), undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Taggard, Genevieve, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Talmadge, Eugene, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Terrel, Mary Church, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Thalmann, Ernst, undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Thomas, Elmer, undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Thomas, J. Parnell (John Parnell), undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Thomas, Norman, undated (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Thomas, R. J. (Rolland Jay), undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Thompson, Robert I, undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Thompson, Robert II, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Thoreau, Henry David, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Thorez, Maurice, undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Tighe, Michael F., undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Tito, Josip Broz, undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Togliatti, Palmiro, 1956, undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Toller, Ernst, undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Tormey, Betty Gannett, undated (Box 2, Folder 138a)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Toy, Harry S., undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Truman, Bess Wallace, undated (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Truman, Harry S., undated (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Tubman, Harriet, undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Twain, Mark, undated (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Tyner, Jarvis, undated (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Tyson, Ronald, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Vaillant-Couturier, Marie-Claude, undated (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Van Arsdale, Harry, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Van Fleet, James A. (James Alward), undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Van Nuys, Frederick, undated (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Vandenburg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), undated (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Velde, Harold Himmel, undated (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Vinson, Fred M., undated (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Vivian, C. T., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferdinand), undated (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Wallace, George C. (George Corley), 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Henry Agard), undated (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Walter, Francis E. (Francis Eugene), undated (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Warren, Earl, undated (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Washington, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Wason, Robert R. (Robert Ross), undated (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Weinberg, Sidney J. (Sidney James), undated (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Weinstock, Louis, undated (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Weir, Ernest Tener, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Weisenburger, ?, undated (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Welles, Sumner, undated (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Weygand, Maxine, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Whalen, Grover A. (Grover Aloysius), undated (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Wheatley, Phillis, undated (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Wheeler, Burton K. (Burton Kendall), undated (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Whitman, Walt, undated (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Whitney, Anita, undated (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Whittier, John Greenleaf, undated (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Williams, Aubrey Willis, undated (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Williams, Smokey Joe, undated (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Wilson, Charles Edward, undated (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Wilson, Charles Erwin, undated (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Windsor, Edward, Duke of, undated (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Winehell, Walter, undated (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Winston, Henry, undated (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Winter, Carl, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Wirt, William A. (William Albert), undated (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Wood, Robert E. (Robert Elkington), undated (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Wortis, Rose, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Wright, Robert, undated (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Zhukov, Georgii Konstantinovich, undated (Box 2, Folder 185)
- Series II: Subject Cartoons, 1937-2000
  Series II: Subject Cartoons consists of cartoons filed by hundreds of different subjects. This series is divided into two subseries, the first of which contains cartoons that were pulled from the Daily Worker and Daily World Photograph Collection (PHOTOS 223). The folder titles that the cartoons came out of were retained in this sub-series. The material ranges in date from 1937-1988, but for the most part is undated. The second subseries contains another set of cartoons arranged by subject. These presumably were used as a cartoon and graphic filing system for the Daily Worker/Daily World.
  - Subseries A: Daily Worker/Daily World Subject Cartoons, 1937-1988
    This subseries consists of original and pre-press drawings. Roughly half the folders contain signed artwork. Artists that have considerable representation in this subseries include: Eric (James Erickson), Hayle, Sam Hill, Hal Kinkaid, and Snow (Haile Hendrix). Subjects represented in the cartoons are diverse and range from the Black Panthers, civil rights, and women to housing, the Ku Klux Klan, and labor history. The topics in the subject series are as diverse as the Daily Worker/Daily World's coverage.
    - African Americans: United States History, undated (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - African Americans: Voting Discrimination, undated (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Agriculture, undated (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: JP Stevens Boycott, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - American Bar Association (ABA), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - American History: Space: Strategic Defense Initiative, undated (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - Automation, undated (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - Babies, undated (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - Beaches and Pools, undated (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Bible: Illustrations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Biological and Chemical Warfare, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Black Panthers, 1969, undated (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - Bombings, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - Bosses, undated (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Children, undated (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Chile: Demonstrations for, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - China, 1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - China: Army and Navy, undated (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Christian Crusade, undated (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Civil Rights, 1966, undated (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Colonialism, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America, 1974, undated (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA): 21st Convention, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Corporations, 1969, undated (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Crime, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - Daily Worker, 1964-1967, undated (Box 2, Folder 211)
    - Daily Worker: Column Headings and Masthead, 1967, undated (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Daily Worker: Bazaars, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Daily World, 1975-1980, undated (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - Daily World: Column Headings and Masthead, 1968-1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Daily World: Picnics, 1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Party: Watergate Scandal, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Disarmament, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Draft: Demonstrations Against, 1967, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Drugs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Education and Students, 1964-1972, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Elections and Voting, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Factories, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Farms/ Farming, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Fascism: United States, 1945-1952 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Federal Republic of Germany: Berlin, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Federal Republic of Germany: Rearmament, unated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Food, 1972-1975, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Food Service Industry and Workers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Foreign Citizens: Immigrants, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - France: Revolution, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Freedom Riders: Demonstrations for, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Funerals, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Garment Workers, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Germany: Third Reich, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Greece, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Hands, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Health and Medicine, 1973-1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Hippies, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Homelessness, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Hospitals, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - House Committee on Un-American Activities (HUAC) (United States House of Representatives Committee on Un-American Activities), 1948, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - House Painters, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Housing, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Hunger, undated (Box Tamiment Shared MSXOS002, Folder 1)
    - Integration: Demonstrations for, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation (ITC), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Israel, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Italy: Ancient Rome, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Jefferson Bookshop (New York, NY), undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Jim Crow, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Ku Klux Klan, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Labor History, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Labor Management Relations Act: Demonstrations against, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Labor Organizations, 1987, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Labor Organizations: AFL-CIO, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Labor Organizations: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Labor Organizations: AFT: Rapp-Coudert Committee, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Labor Organizations: CIO Conventions, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Labor Organizations: Strikes, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Labor Organizations: UAW-Strikes-GM, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Labor Organizations: UFWA, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Labor Youth League, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Latin America, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Liquor Industry, 1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Longshoremen, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Loyalty Oath, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Ludlow Massacre, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Lumber Industry and Workers, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - March on Washington, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - May Day Parade and Celebrations, 1979, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - McCarran Act, 1956-1962, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Miners and Mining Industry, 1968, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Money, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Movies/ Theater, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Music, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Napalm- Demonstrations against, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - National Association of Manufacturers: United Business Committee, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - National Maritime Union (NMU), undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Nature, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - New York Daily News, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Newspaper Industry and Workers, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Newsstands and Newsdealers, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Nuclear Weapons, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Nuclear Weapons: Explosives, undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Oil Industry and Workers, 1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Oil Industry and Workers: Demonstrations Against, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Peace, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Pentagon, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - People, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Police, 1971, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Poor People's Campaign, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Population Explosion, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Portugal, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Prisoners, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Profile Drawings, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Profits, undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Progressive Party, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Puerto Rico: Independence Movement, undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Racial Unity, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Racism, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Radio, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Railroad Industry and Workers, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Republican Party, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Rosenberg Case, undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Sacco and Vanzetti Trial, undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Scabs- Strikebreaking, undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - School Information, undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - School Integration: Demonstrations for, undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Shaving, undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Sheep and Goats, undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Ships and Boats, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Smith Act (Alien Registration Act), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Smith Act- Trial of 1949 (Foley Square Trial), undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Soldiers, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Soviet Union: Anti-Soviet Propaganda, undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Soviet Union: Foreign Relations: United States, 1974-1988 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Soviet Union: Satire, undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Soviet Union: Science, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Space, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Sports: Baseball, undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Sports: Bowling, undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Statue of Liberty, undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Steel Industry and Workers, undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Stockholm Appeal (World Peace Council), undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Strikes, undated (Box 3, Folder 108b)
    - Subways, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Summer, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Taiwan, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Taxes, 1966-1970, undated (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Television, 1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Trade, undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire (New York, NY), 1911 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Trotskyites, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Unemployment, 1970, 1975, undated (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Unions, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - United States: Air Force, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - United States: Army, undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - United States: Congress, undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - United States: Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - United States: History, undated (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - United States: History: Founding Documents, undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - United States: Imperialism, 1968-1975 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Various Subjects I, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Various Subjects II, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Various Subjects III, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Various Subjects IV, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Various Subjects V, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Various Subjects VI, undated (Box 3, Folder 125a)
    - Vietnam War, 1963-1971, undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Vietnam War: Demonstrations Against: United States, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Vietnam War: United States Atrocities: My Lai Massacre, undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Washington (D.C.), 1973, undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Water and Water Pollution, undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Wealth/ Luxury, undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Welfare, undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Witch Hunts I, undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Witch Hunts II, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Women, undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Women: Feminist Movements, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Women: Housewives, undated (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Women: Housework, undated (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Women: Mothers, undated (Box 3, Folder 137b)
    - Women Workers, undated (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - The Worker, undated (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Workers, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Workers: African-Americans: Men, undated (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Workers: African-Americans: Women, undated (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Workers' Bookshop (New York, NY), undated (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - World War I, undated (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - World War II: Pearl Harbor, undated (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Young Workers Liberation League, 1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Subseries B: General Subject Cartoons, 1947-2000
    This subseries contains cartoons from 1947-2000, and consists chiefly of copies of cartoons. The original order of this subseries was maintained. Ostensibly the files were a graphic and cartoon filing system for the Daily Worker/Daily World and its later incarnations. An index to the cartoons can be found at the beginning of the subseries.
    - Cartoons: Index, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Originals, 1996, undated (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Administration, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - African-Americans, 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Anti-Communism, 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Arms I, 1980-1991, undated (Box 3A, Folder 1)
    - Arms II, 1984-1985 (Box 3A, Folder 2)
    - Banks, 1986-1996, undated (Box 3A, Folder 3)
    - Blashko, Abe (artist), undated (Box 3A, Folder 4)
    - Books, undated (Box 3A, Folder 5)
    - Born Again Budget, 1980 (Box 3A, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1981-1995 (Box 3A, Folder 7)